Ghostbusters
If there's something strange in your neighborhood
Who you gonna call?
If there's something weird and it don't look good
I ain't afraid of no ghost
If you're seeing things running through your head
Who can you call?
An invisible man sleeping in your bed
Aoh, who you gonna call?
I ain't afraid of no ghost
Who you gonna call?
If you're all alone pick up the phone and call
I ain't afraid of no ghost
Uh, I hear it likes the girls
Who you gonna call?
Mmh if you have a dose of a freaky ghost baby you'd better call aw
Let me tell you something bustin' makes me feel good
I ain't afraid of no ghost
Don't get caught alone no no
When it comes through your door
Unless you just want some more
I think you better call
Aw, who you gonna call?
Who you gonna call?
I think you better call
He he
Who you gonna call?
I can't hear you
Louder
Who can you call?
Uh, he likes the girls too
Who you gonna call?
Who can you call?